♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?
♪ Lucky there's a family guy
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us
♪ Laugh and cry
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
You guys, don't you think
I'm a little old
for the Teen Choice Awards?
I mean, I turned 18 today.
Oh, come on, Meg.
You always used to love
the Teen Choice Awards.
Yeah, ever since Fox
pulled this contrived night
of (bleep) out of
their ass, in an effort
to get in on the awards
show business,
it's been very
special to you.
ANNOUNCER: Coming to you live, it's
the Teen Choice Awards!
Featuring...
(girls scream)
I tell ya, every year, I
recognize fewer and fewer names.
(girls scream)
(girls continue to scream
with each announcement)
And a live performance by...
Plus we tally your text vote
for the Biggest Whiff
and Choice Bro-ment
of the Year!
And now your host...
Wavyhair Doucheston!
(girls screaming)
I touched him!
What's up, Teen Choice Awards?!
We're gonna kick things off
with Choice Lacrosse Guy Smile!
Give it up for our first
presenter, Wilford Brimley!
It's entirely too loud in here!
Quiet down!
There's no accountability
anymore!
I have diabetes!
Hey, what do you say we get
some music in here, huh?
No, that'll only
make things worse!
Give it up for our first
nominated Choice Band
of the Night,
Peehole Skin!
(rock music plays)
♪ (grunts) Feelings
(girls scream)
I'm gonna put
a stop to this!
(all screaming in fear)
Well, that was
unfortunate.
Hey, what's with all
the cars on the street?
Oh, they're all here
for your surprise party, Meg.
Peter, for God's
sake, you idiot!
We were supposed
to open the door
so everyone could
yell "surprise!"
Surprise!
Oh... Oh, dear.
Mom, if it's a surprise party,
where is everybody?
(hushed):
Chris, what the hell?!
I thought you were
gonna pay the kids
from school to show up!
I gave you $300!
Why do you think
Dad's here?
Hey, Meg, happy birthday.
You're the coolest.
Well, then what are all the cars
doing out there?
Oh, they must be
for Mort's party.
Okay, the first rule
of Jewish fight club
is if somebody says,
"Ow," you stop.
Ow!
Okay, let's eat.
I'm really sorry
about this, honey.
I-It looks like
nobody's coming.
But we had fun at the Teen
Choice Awards, right?
I guess.
Well, I guess we
ought to call it a night.
Come on, Stewie.
Up to bed.
No party? Oh, come on.
I was gonna show a slide show
of all those silly photos
I took of Meg.
Well, happy birthday
anyway, Meg.
See you in the morning.
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Quagmire.
What's going on?
Well, Peter,
a little birdie told me
that today is
Meg's birthday.
You giving me credit?
Yeah, I just told him.
I'm the one
who told him.
So where is
the birthday girl?
Oh, hi, Mr. Quagmire.
Oh, please,
my father is Mr. Quagmi--
Oh, no. He's... Okay,
well, he used
to be Mr. Quagmire.
Now he's, how he's
just Ida Davis.
Anyway, this is a special day
for you, young lady.
Here's a gift for ya.
A scented candle?
As a girl,
I love this!
That was originally $30.
Thanks, Mr. Quagmire.
Well, it's your
18th birthday, Meg.
That's a very important
milestone in
a young girl's...
I mean, a young
woman's life.
Hey, welcome
to the adult club, huh?
And you know what?
You got another member
right next door
if you ever want
to talk and stuff.
Happy birthday.
Hey... Hey, where's
that pinky going, huh?
Where's he going?
Wha, what's he doing?
Get back here.
There you go.
Look at Quagmire hitting
on that skank.
You know he's gonna
close the deal.
Peter, that skank is
your daughter.
Oh, my God,
you're right!
You know, Meg,
I'd love to see you
without your hat on.
Okay.
So, anyway, I'm on approach
into Lambert Field
in some of the worst turbulence
I've ever flown through.
I mean, I have never seen
anything like it.
Everyone in the cabin
was, like, "Aah!"
but I kept my cool.
I trusted my training,
and brought the plane in safely,
and in fact,
it turned out, ironically,
to be one of the smoothest
landings I've ever made.
Well, gosh, Quagmire,
this has been a fun night,
but I guess, uh, you better be
getting home now, huh?
Yeah, it is getting late
I guess I'll go home
and rub out a giggity.
Take it easy, you guys.
See you later, Meg.
(clicks tongue)
Bye.
Okay, that was weird.
That was weird.
Right?
Oh, my God,
so weird.
I tell you something,
if he touches my daughter,
I'm gonna be kicking butts
and taking names!
And then giving
those names
to other people
whose butts I kick.
What's your name?
Derek.
Michael.
You're Derek now!
(phone beeps)
(phone chimes)
Oh! (chuckles)
(phone beeps)
(phone chimes)
Okay, Glenn,
time to reel her in.
(phone beeps)
(phone chimes)
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God!
Ah, it's too much, too much.
(phone beeps)
I love stars!
We now return to Grainy Footage
of a Potential Bigfoot
that will surely spark a lively
debate in your household.
Oh, my God!
That is real!
No, total fake.
(all talking at once)
Look at that. That is obviously
a suit. It's a fraud.
Look at the way it walks.
Totally fake.
Why would somebody
make that up, Lois?
What's in it for them?
(knocking)
Oh, hey, Mr. G.
How's it going?
Quagmire, what are you
doing here?
Hi, Glenn.
Bye, you guys.
Me and Glenn
are going out.
What?! Like
hell you are!
Don't worry, Dad!
I'll take care of him!
Stay away from my sis!
Okay, you two have
fun on your date.
What?!
Drive carefully.
We'll see you later.
Lois, are you out
of your mind?!
We can't let Quagmire
take Meg out on a date!
That guy'll bang anything.
Hey, Lois, I'm starving.
What's for dinner?
I made meatloaf.
It's in the fridge.
Hey, Peter, do you mind?
But I have
to get dinner.
Go out!
Peter, nothing's
gonna happen.
Don't you see?
She's only doing this
to get a rise out of us.
If we fight her on it,
she'll only push further.
Well, she may not plan
on sleeping with him,
but you don't know how
smooth Quagmire is, Lois.
He's like a vagician.
Oh, that's clever.
I know! Isn't it?
He practices vagic.
"Vagician" was funnier.
Okay, well, the point is,
we ought to be worried.
Peter, trust me.
I know what's going on
in her head.
It's just a game.
I used to do the same
thing to my parents.
The problem is,
they pushed back,
and the results
were not good.
Mr. Pewterschmidt,
we pumped your
daughter's stomach
and we found vodka, Rohypnol,
a fair amount of DNA
that is not her own
and a class ring.
Harvard?
I think it was
SUNY something.
Oh, I don't want
to hear any more!
So how're
your studies going?
They're going
pretty good.
School's good.
What's your favorite class?
What was your
favorite class?
Okay, let's say it
at the same time
and see if they're
the same.
Okay, one, two, three.
Hist... math!
Math!
Oh, my God, we have
so much in common!
Do you have any brothers
or sisters?
Yeah, I have
two brothers.
Aw, they sound
terrific.
Hey, you want to blow
this joint?
Sure.
Oh, wow, really?!
All right, go for it!
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, oh, you,
you mean leave.
No, yeah, sure.
No, let's go.
Gosh, Meg, I sure had
a swell time with you.
Me, too, Glenn.
God, it's so amazing
that you've been my dad's friend
for, like, years,
and now we have this connection.
Hey, do you want
to come in
for some Crystal Light
or something?
Well, I do believe in me,
but it's getting kind of late.
Um, I really want to
see you again, though.
Oh, you know it.
Oh, God, Peter!
Scared the
hell out of me!
What're you doing here?
I think you know.
Did you have sex
with my daughter?
What? Come on, Peter.
Did you have sex
with my daughter?!
Peter, trust me,
it's not happening.
(sighs)
All right. Good.
Yeah, she's really making
me work for it.
Maybe you could
talk to her.
Well, I'll try,
but sometimes she can be
as stubborn as a mule.
I tell you, you tell her
to do something once,
she does the opposite.
You know, it's like
she ain't even heard you
in the first place.
It's like talking
to a brick wall.
Worse than talking...
Even a brick wall doesn't tell
you they understand you,
and then go do the opposite,
you know?
So it's no surprise to me
that you're having
these difficulties.
That-that just seems
to be the way she is.
You know, whether it's just
that she's not listening
or whether it's that she's
making a conscious decision
to defy your wishes,
who can say, you know?
And I would say,
in some respects,
having a strong-willed kid
is a good thing,
but it can get frustrating
as hell on the other side.
So, you know, lieve me,
I hear loud and clear
where you're--
Wait a second!
No, I won't talk to her!
And I want you to stay the hell
away from her!
Peter it's me-- Quagmire.
This is what I do.
Besides, Meg is 18 now
and you've gotta let go.
You've done your job.
It's my turn now.
Look, Quagmire, you're
one of my best pals,
and I'm asking you
not to do this.
I want to help you,
Peter, I really do,
but it's-- it's like you're
asking a fish not to swim.
She's legal and I'm going in.
Well, we'll see about that.
I ain't afraid
to stand up to friends.
Just ask Spartacus.
I'm Spartacus.
That guy's
Spartacus.
ANNOUNCER: We now return to Two Lame
Chicks on Vacation in Mexico.
Oh, my God, don't
drink the water.
I'm so going to brush
my teeth with tequila.
Mexico!
Hey, is this beach topless?
No, but my
margarita's bottomless.
Mexico!
That cute guy's been
staring at you all night.
Oh, my God. I'm going to go poo
now, so I don't have to later.
Mexico!
Hey, you want to see
my pictures from Mexico?
Look, Janine, I just-- this is--
I can't with you anymore.
It's all the time.
This is a job.
Please take off
that silly hat.
(phone ringing)
GIRL: Mexico!
I... I can't talk right now.
You okay?
Yeah, babe.
I got to pee,
but I don't want to move.
I'm so comfortable right now.
I can pause it.
I guess you could
pause it...
but you can't pause me!
Fast forward.
Glenn, stop.
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe either.
This is torture
for me, too.
No fair. Stop.
I'm going to...
(farts)
Sorry.
Ah, that's all right.
It's just your body.
Sometimes things slip out.
Probably just making
room for something.
Like what?
Hey, gang, got room for one more
right in the middle of you two?
Come on, scooch apart, there.
Ooh, what's this?
Quagmire's cell phone?
Well, now that you're with Meg,
you don't need to be talking to,
uh, "Backbush" anymore.
Oh, and I'll send a text to
"Possible Nipple Ring"
saying you're off the market.
(phone beeps)
You're "Possible Nipple Ring"?
All right, well, I better
send a text to "Backbush."
(buzzing)
Oh, come on.
I'm "Backbush"?
This can't be a
surprise to you, Peter.
Yeah, I knew.
(sobbing):
I just didn't know you knew.
Okay, what compound is this?
That's sodium chloride.
That's right.
How about this one?
Hydrogen peroxide.
God, you're so smart.
How about this one?
QM2? I'm not sure
what that is.
It's Quag-megium.
It's the strongest
compound on Earth.
Nothing can separate it.
It has an atomic weight
of awesome.
You're such a
cutie patootie.
If I'm a cutie patootie, then
you're a peenie-vageenie.
Aww!
I heard a cute "aw" in there.
Cool down!
Meg, there's something
we need to talk about.
Dad, I swear to God, I thought
you could flush those things.
Meg, you ever heard
of Joan Van Ark?
No.
Here's a picture
of Joan Van Ark.
Oh, my God, she's gorgeous.
Gorgeous. Yes.
Yes, Meg, gorgeous.
Yes.
Every man wanted her.
But one man got her.
A man she trusted to keep her
safe and beautiful forever.
That man was Glenn Quagmire.
And two short months later,
this is what happened
to Joan Van Ark.
Oh! Oh, my God!
I don't want this
to happen to you, Meg.
I don't want you to turn
into a hilarious photograph.
Dad, I know what
you're trying to do,
and I want you
to stop it.
Mom!
What is it, Meg?
Mom, tell Dad
to leave me alone.
I'm 18, and he keeps
treating me like a kid.
Peter, I told you not to push
her about this Quagmire thing.
If you push too hard,
you're going to push her
right into his arms.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Nothing.
This is a big game
Meg is playing,
and the only way to win
is not to play it.
Is that a WarGames reference?
Might be.
You know WarGames?
Yeah.
Still finding out
new stuff about you.
That's the adventure.
There's a nerd in there.
Maybe there is.
I might bang her later.
How about a nice
game of chess?
I prefer banging.
Dad, have you seen my book bag?
What, Chris?
(screaming)
Oh, Peter, there you are.
Would you go tell Meg
that lunch is on the table?
Oh, Meg's not here.
What do you mean?
She and Quagmire went up
to his cabin for the weekend.
What?!
Yeah, I drew you
a crude flip book
to explain what's happening.
Okay, I got
a little off track there,
but they went to his cabin.
Peter, Quagmire has
a name for that cabin.
He calls it his sex cabin.
No, he doesn't.
He calls it "The Stuffet Inn."
Oh, my God, I can't believe
you knew about this
and you let her go.
Hey, don't give me that crap.
I'm doing exactly
what you told me to do.
You said don't mess with her
business, so I didn't.
Peter, this is different.
It's one thing to
rebelliously flaunt an older guy
in front of your parents,
but it's a whole other thing
to go away with him for the
weekend to his sex cabin.
Oh, is that right?
Oh, don't worry, Peter, he's
not going to sleep with her.
That's you. Nerd.
Look, everyone knows if you go
away with a guy for the weekend
and don't have sex with him,
you're a huge bitch.
We got to stop them.
So you admit you were wrong.
Yes.
You admit you were stupid.
Yes, yes.
You admit all women are stupid.
No.
All right, I'll take
what I can get.
Come on.
To the Peter-dactyl.
(screeching)
(buzzing, crackling)
Oh, no, now I got
to take care of the babies.
Look, Peter,
his car's still there.
Maybe they haven't left yet.
Quagmire, let me in,
you son of a bitch.
QUAGMIRE (recorded): I'm sorry
I'm not home to receive you.
The reason being that you have
sufficiently scared me away
from your wife or daughter.
I plan to get help and use
better judgment in the future.
Wait a minute, so Quagmire
just changed all of a
sudden, just like that?
You want me to read this or not?
No, Grandpa, I don't.
No kid wants to be read
anything any more.
Computers exist.
It's just you won't leave.
Okay, where were we?
Quagmire's front door.
You think they're
hiding in there?
(engine revving)
Oh, no! Peter, look.
See you later, suckers.
Oh, good luck to them.
Peter!
Oh, right, right.
Let's go.
(tires squealing)
(horns honking)
We're never going
to get up there.
I wonder what's causing
all this traffic.
Oh, boy.
Yep, there's the problem.
Not drawn yet.
Come on, guys.
Really? Let's go.
What the hell's
going on up there?
(snoring)
What...? Yep. Yep.
(owl hooting)
So tell the truth.
Have you brought
other women up here before?
Honestly? Two.
Really?
Yep, I brought the ashes
of my third grade teacher,
Mrs. Nicholson, and spread
them across the lake,
per her last request.
Oh.
The other was some skag
I met on a dock
four miles from here.
What?!
(imitates buzzer)
Strike four, Jelly Jealouson.
The other was my sister.
(both laughing)
(sighs)
It's so nice up here.
I know.
I love the way the fire
makes the shadows dance around
behind us.
One time, my friends
and I went camping,
and nobody could
start a campfire,
and then I tried to start
the campfire, and I could.
That's insane.
Wha-- what is going on
over here?
Wha-- are we taking
our shirts off now?
Okay, follow the leader.
Come on, Peter, hurry!
Wait wait,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
(loon calling)
Listen to that.
It's a loon.
That's beautiful.
You know, we ought to get
a (bleep) cabin up here.
Peter, we're wasting time.
Quagmire's in there about to
have sex with our daughter.
That son of a bitch.
Let's-- wait-- w-wait
a minute, do you hear that?
I don't hear anything.
I know.
Isn't it bliss?
Peter, let's go!
Mm. Thanks for
the ice cream, Glenn.
And you're right, somehow
it does taste better
in my underpants.
Yeah, it's like being
at the beach, huh?
Now get over here while
the inside of your mouth
is still freezing cold.
There you are,
you son of a bitch!
You get away from
my daughter, you pervert!
Meg, get in the car,
we're going home.
I'm not going home!
I'm 18, and you can't tell
me what to do anymore.
Meg, I'm only going
to say this once.
You may be an adult,
but you're still my daughter,
and it's my job to protect
you from errant wieners.
So, I don't care
how old you are,
you're going to do what I say
and get in the damn car!
Yes, Daddy.
If you ever touch
my daughter again,
I will cut your thing off
and feed it to Brian.
Okay.
And Peter and I get this cabin
for one weekend a month.
Do you understand me?
Yes, ma'am.
Peter, I got us the cabin.
Yay.
I don't want to see your
face knocking on our door
for at least a month.
Would you sign the
guest book on your way out?
Lois... Griffin.
Peter... Griffin.
We... heard... a loon.
You know, Mom and Dad, I'm
really glad that you kept me
from doing what
I was going to do.
Well, that's what
parents are for, Meg.
No matter what age you are.
We love you and we just
never want to see you hurt.
I only wish I'd seen
what was going on
from the start,
like your father did.
Well, I know the signs...
because the same thing
happened to me.
An older neighbor.
Her name was Elaine.
I was 18 and my body was firm
from push-ups and sit-ups.
I was stunning.
But while my body was mature,
I had the mind of a 12-year-old.
Elaine invited me over
with the promise of pie.
Little did I know
this would lead
to an eight-year-long
psychosexual entanglement.
She's probably dead now.
Life's funny sometimes.
And... scene.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru